

#### **About**

Creative graphic designer with innovative ideas and a unique approach to visuals. More than 3 years of experience developing designs for print media, Social media, Animations, and advertising. Solid understanding of marketing principles and advertising techniques. Great attention to detail and a talent for creating memorable visual designs.

#### Contact

- +92-301-4191554
- wshafique6@gmail.com
- Super Town, Lahore

#### Education

**BS Information Technology** University of Education, Lahore 2016 - 2020

DAE (Electronics) PBTE, Lahore 2013 - 2016

#### **Interest**







# Waseem Shafique

## Multimedia Graphic Designer

https://www.behance.net/waseemshafique

+92-301-4191554

### **Experience**

#### Sr. Graphic Designer | Animator | Video Editor

The Game Storm Studios (Pvt.) Ltd / Arfa Tower / 2022 - present

Creating high-quality graphics, animations, and visuals for social media posts, cover images, banners, advertisements, and other promotional materials. This could involve using tools like Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, after effects and premiere pro.

#### Sr. Graphic Designer | Animator | Video Editor

OZI Technology / Arfa Tower / 2022 - present

Working with the Branding Team to make social media content and **Event branding** 

#### Multimedia Graphic Designer - 2D Animator

Checkmate De Studio / Lahore Cannt / 2022 - 2022 (6 Months)

Design Social media Post and animation for Pakistan Leading Cosmetics Brands Like Mazton, Biocos and Mark 30.

#### Graphic Designer - 2D Animator

Filmbaily-Creative Agency / Johar Town / 2021 - 2022

Designing Social meida post and animation for Brands, Packgning desing and print media work.

#### **Graphic Designer Team Lead**

TechnoCues / DHA-3 / 2020 - 2021

Social Media Post Designer for local and international clients.

#### Skills











